# **Ahmed Saber Fathy**

Desouk, Kafr El Sheikh, Egypt (GMT+2)

**J** +20 120 861 1892

<u>ahmed0saber33@gmail.com</u>

https://github.com/ahmed0saber

in <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/ahmed0saber/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/ahmed0saber/</a>

## Summary

Hello there, My name is Ahmed Saber, I'm a 2-year experienced React.js Frontend Web Developer who enjoys building everything with JavaScript. In this duration, I have learned a lot of technologies, created many cool websites, collaborated with great developers and contributed to open source projects.

So I'm always seeking to have an opportunity that matches my skills, to make the best use of all what I have learned.

### **Skills**

> HTML5

> JavaScript ES6

Bootstrap

> ISON

> React.js

> CSS3

> jQuery

> SASS

> Electron.js

> Next.js

## Languages

- > Arabic native
- > English conversational

## **Experience**

> Frontend Web Developer - Full-Time

Valinteca - Remote April 2022 - Present

> React JS Developer - Internship

Across The Globe (ATG) - Remote

April 2022 - Present

## **Education**

> Bachelor of Science: Physics

Kafr El Sheikh university - Kafr El Sheikh - Egypt

Undergraduate, 2019 - 2023

# **Projects**

#### > My Portfolio

That's my personal website where I show my skills and projects.

- Built with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6, JSON, React.js
- View at <a href="https://ahmed0saber.onrender.com">https://ahmed0saber.onrender.com</a>

#### > XO Online

XO game where you can play vs easy or hard bot, vs local or online player, chat with people, invite them, win more games and rank up.

- Built with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6
- View at <a href="https://xo-online.herokuapp.com">https://xo-online.herokuapp.com</a>

#### > TestMode

A website where you can test your skills in some technologies related to programming and get certified.

- Built with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6, JSON, React.js, Next.js
- View at <a href="https://testmode.vercel.app">https://testmode.vercel.app</a>

## **Community Activities**

- > Frontend Web Development Trainee GDSC Assuit university, 2021-2022
- > Frontend Web Development Trainee MSP Al Azhar university, 2021-2022
- > Frontend Web Development Instructor Az-SENCS, 2022-2023

### **Certificates**

- > FreeCodeCamp certified Frontend Web Developer
- Verify at

https://github.com/ahmed0saber/certifications/tree/main/Freecodecamp

- > EgFWD certified Web Designer
- Verify at

https://github.com/ahmed0saber/certifications/blob/main/egfwd-challenger.pdf